

Onuoha lfechinyere Uzochukwu

Creative Designer & Branding Expert

jobs@onuohaui.works +234 81 3734 271 0 Abuja, Nigeria linkedin.com/in/onuohaui

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite Canva [Verified by Canva] Fontself **Figma** Notion HTML 5 CSS 3 Python PowerPoint

INTERESTS

Product Design & Research Human-Centered Design **Visual Communication** Internet Health New Media

LANGUAGES

English Spanish [Basic]

ABOUT ME

Graphics Design Leader with 7 years of experience eager to help launch a new creative direction with captivating static assets.

Multidisciplinary experiences have enabled me to contribute across companies throughout my career and will undoubtedly provide immense value to your organisational goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CANVA 2019 - Present

INDEPENDENT CONTRACTOR, TEMPLATE CREATOR & CONTRIBUTOR

- Designed over 200+ original graphics, icons & elements utilizing different styles and approaches all of which are published in the Canva public template library.
- Facilitated design training on "Storytelling for Change Makers" for the Canva Non-profit Arm.
- Responsible for creating periodic video tutorials for Canva Design School.

FREELANCE DESIGNER

2012 - Present UX/UI DESIGN, LOGO DESIGN, CORPORATE BRANDING, RESEARCH

- Provided graphic design services across digital, video, and print for 25+ clients in the tech, sales, marketing, and consulting space.
- Designed custom layout, artwork, elements and typography using Illustrator, CorelDraw, In-Design and Canva to meet Brand standards [link to freelance portfolio].

MAPEMOND RESOURCES

2018 - 2020

- BRAND DESIGNER, ADVERTISER & DIGITAL SKILLS TRAINER
- Developed campaign and tracked campaign analysis to ensure that they meet marketing goals.
- -Designed art, layouts, color story, and typography in line with Brand vision.
- Spearheaded creative design projects by providing creative briefs to generate visual concepts and designs for clients by effectively managing work flow and providing status reports through oral and written communication.
- Facilitated digital skills training, creative review meetings and ideation sessions.
- Provided quality control over projects within tight deadlines while working with junior designers.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

MATHEMATICS EDUCATION & COMPUTER SCIENCE

2009 - 2012 FCE(T) BICHI

- Graduated 2012
- TRCN certified

GOOGLE 2017

- Digital Marketing Fundamentals
- Google Educators Training (In-view)

BRITISH COUNCIL DIGITAL FELLOW

2018

DIGITAL MARKETER INSTITUTE

Certified Direct-Response Copywriting Specialist

2020